jamtrackcentral.com 2017-02-23

# Pages | Jamtrackcentral

We at JamTrackCentral Ltd take the issue of your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy sets out how we will treat the personal information which you have provided to us while using the website located at www.jamtrackcentral.com (the “Site”) or the services provided via the Site (the “Services”). We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes will take effect from the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Site.

To properly provide the Services, it is necessary for us to hold and process personal information. We shall take reasonable care in keeping this information secure and preventing any unauthorised access or unlawful use of it. All personal information is processed by us in accordance with data protection legislation applicable in the UK and the EU.

We will only keep your personal information for as long as is necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was given to us.

We may ask you to provide some or all of the following: details of your name, company name, address, telephone/facsimile number(s), e-mail address and credit card details. This personal information will be stored together with any additional information you may provide to us from time to time, and will be used to provide you with the Services and other services associated with the Site. However, credit card information is not stored by JamTrackCentral Ltd in any way. We may also use your personal information to:-

1\. Analyse use of our web sites

2\. Keep you up to date with services provided by JamTrackCentral Ltd and our trusted partners which we think may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive this information, simply check the box at the checkout stage.

We may use “cookies” while you access the Services. These are used to avoid the need to re-enter details on different occasions.

We may transfer your personal data for internal business purposes to locations outside the European Economic Area, some of which may have different data protection laws to the UK, or no data protection laws. Please note that in respect of information transmitted to the US, we shall endeavour to transmit such information only to entities that comply with suitable policies.

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or wish to resume receiving information which you may have previously opted out of receiving, please contact us at admin@jamtrackcentral.com or at: JamTrackCentral Ltd, 3 Clos Cae FFynon, North Cornelly, Bridgend, South Wales, CF33 4HX.
